Guide to the Annina Nosei Gallery Archive 1963-2009 MSS.298
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Artist Files, 1963-2004; 200736
  - Subseries A: General Artist Files, 204161
    - Sandro Chia, 1979-1983; 207764 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Chuck Connelly [From "Chuck Connelly 1989" Letter Box], 1985-1987; 207765 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Chuck Connelly - Book [From "Chuck Connelly 1989" Letter Box], 1986-1994; 207766 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Chuck Connelly - Press [From "Chuck Connelly 1989" Letter Box], 1985-1996; 207767 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Chuck Connelly - Correspondence; Sept. 1986- [From "Chuck Connelly 1989" Letter Box], 1984-1986; 207768 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Chuck Connelly - Correspondence; Sept. 1984-Aug. 1986 [From "Chuck Connelly 1989" Letter Box], 1984-1986; 207769 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Paolo Colombo, 1977-1984; 207772 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Jan Commandeur, 1985-1999; 207773 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - George Condo, 1983, 1984; 207774 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - D, 1980-1995; 207775 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Santolo De Luca, 1998-2000; 207776 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - David Deutsch - Correspondence [From "Deutsch" Letter Box], 1982, 1983; 207777 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - David Deutsch - Press [From "Deutsch" Letter Box], undated; 207778 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - David Deutsch - Inventory [From "Deutsch" Letter Box], 1982, 1983; 207779 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - [Loose Material from "Deutsch" Letter Box] [1/4], 1982-1984; 207780 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - [Loose Material from "Deutsch" Letter Box] [2/4], 1983, 1984; 207781 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - [Loose Material from "Deutsch" Letter Box] [3/4], 1983; 207782 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - [Loose Material from "Deutsch" Letter Box] [4/4], 1983; 207783 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Martin Disler, 1981, 1984; 207784 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Arturo Duclos, 1992-1995; 207785 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Arturo Duclos Correspondence [1/2], 1993-1995; 207786 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Arturo Duclos Correspondence [2/2], 1993-1995; 207787 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Marcel Duchamp, 1963, 1966, 1980; 207788 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - E F, 1980-1996; 207789 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - [Rainer Fetting - Letter from Annina Nosei], 1983; 207790 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Eric Fischl, 1980-1982; 207791 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Dan Flavin, 1963-1982; 207792 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Flechemuller Press, 1984-1997; 207793 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Flechemuller, 1993-1997; 207794 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Gunther Forg, 1987, 1988; 207795 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Pietro Fortuna [1], 1986; 207796 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Pietro Fortuna [2], 1986; 207797 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - G, 1977-1987; 207798 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Julio Galan - Catalogue 1990, 207799 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - $$ Julio Galan Accounting, 1989-1996; 207800 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Julio Galan Bio/Press Releases, 1992, 1993; 207801 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Julio Galan; Correspondence with Gallery [1/2], 1992-1993; 207802 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Julio Galan; Correspondence with Gallery [2/2], 1992-1997; 207803 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Julio Galan; Correspondence w/ Galleries, Collectors, Institutions, 1990-1996; 207804 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Julio Galan - Press Articles [1/3], 1989-1996; 207805 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Julio Galan - Press Articles [2/3], 1991-1992; 207806 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Julio Galan - Press Articles [3/3], 1989, 1990; 207807 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Gallo - Collectors; Galleries [From "Vincent Gallo" Letter Box], 1999; 207808 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Vincent Gallo [1] [From "Vincent Gallo" Letter Box], 1985; 207809 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Vincent Gallo [2] [From "Vincent Gallo" Letter Box], 1991-1999; 207810 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Vincent Gallo - Correspondence; Jan-Aug. 1986 [From "Vincent Gallo" Letter Box], 1985-1986; 207811 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Vincent Gallo - Correspondence; Sept. 1986 [From "Vincent Gallo" Letter Box], 1986-1989; 207812 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Vincent Gallo - Press Originals [From "Vincent Gallo" Letter Box], 1985-1988; 207813 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Geva/Press, 1990-2001; 207814 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Tsibi Geva Corresp., 1990-2003; 207815 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Mike Glier - Downstairs [From Untitled Letter Box], undated; 207816 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Mike Glier - Corres [From Untitled Letter Box], 1981, 1982; 207817 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Mike Glier [Loose Material from Untitled Letter Box] [1/2], 1981; 207820 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Mike Glier [Loose Material from Untitled Letter Box] [2/2], 1981, 1982; 207821 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - A [Mike Glier] [Loose Material from Untitled Letter Box], undated; 207822 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - B [Mike Glier] [Loose Material from Untitled Letter Box], 1980-1982; 207823 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - C [Mike Glier] [Loose Material from Untitled Letter Box], 1981; 207824 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - D [Mike Glier] [Loose Material from Untitled Letter Box], undated; 207825 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - E F [Mike Glier] [Loose Material from Untitled Letter Box], undated; 207826 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - G [Mike Glier] [Loose Material from Untitled Letter Box], undated; 207827 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - H; I-J [Mike Glier] [Loose Material from Untitled Letter Box], 1982; 207828 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - K; L [Mike Glier] [Loose Material from Untitled Letter Box], undated; 207829 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - R [Mike Glier] [Loose Material from Untitled Letter Box], 1980; 207830 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      Letter boxes had lettered dividers. It is not certain if these were used in any systematic way, but they are preserved here, regardless.
    - Kristen Jones - Andrew Ginzel, 1986-1990; 207831 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Daniele Galiano, 1996-2001; 207832 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Argentina Garofalo, 1996; 207833 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Jose Garofalo, 1995-1998; 207834 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Piero Gilardi, 1968, 1982-1988; 207835 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Patrick Grant, 1999, 2000; 207836 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - K.H. Hodicke - Press, 1980-1986; 207837 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - K.H. Hodicke - Corresp., 1981-1985; 207838 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - H, 1978-1999; 207839 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Keith Haring, 1981-1990; 207840 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Hasper Correspondence, 1997-2004; 207841 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Hasper Press, 1995-2001; 207843 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Steven Harvey, 1987, 1988; 207844 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Fathi Hassan [1], 1994; 207845 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Graciela Hasper, 1997-1999; 207846 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Fathi Hassan [2], 1994, 1995; 207847 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Hal Hirschorn, 1994; 207848 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Lynn Hirschman [Letter Box] [1/2], 1981-1983; 207849 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Lynn Hirschman [Letter Box] [2/2], 1981, 1982; 207850 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - I/J, 1982-1990; 207852 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Neil Jenney, 1978-1984; 207853 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Ronald Gault Jirado [1], 1989-1991; 207854 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Ronald Gault Jirado [2], 1989, 1990; 207855 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Barbara Kruger - reviews, 1986; 207856 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Barbara Kruger catalogs and press, 276120 (Box 59)
    - K, 1980-1991; 207857 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Maki Na Kamura, 2003; 207858 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Betsy Kaufman, 1986-1989; 207859 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Massimo Kaufman, 1989-1992; 207860 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Bernd Koberling [1], 1981-2005; 207861 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Bernd Koberling [2], 2002; 207862 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Joseph Kosuth, 1977-1989; 207863 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - [Kocheisen + Hullmann], undated; 207864 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Jeff Koons, 1981; 207865 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Barbara Kruger Announcements, 1982-1985; 207866 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Barbara Kruger - Correspondence, 1981-1986; 207867 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Barbara Kruger - Press, 1983-1986; 207868 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Barbara Kruger, 1983-1987; 207869 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Kocheisen + Hullman, 1993-1999; 207870 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - [Material from Front Pocket of "Barbara Kruger [Binder 1]"], 1986; 207872 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Barbara Kruger [Binder 1] [1/2], 1985, 1986; 207873 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Barbara Kruger [Binder 1] [2/2], undated; 207874 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - [Material from Back Pocket of "Barbara Kruger [Binder 1]"], 1987; 207875 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - [Material from Front Pocket of "Barbara Kruger [Binder 2]"], undated; 207876 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Barbara Kruger [Binder 2] [1/2], 1985; 207877 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Barbara Kruger [Binder 2] [2/2], undated; 207878 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - [Material from Back Pocket of "Barbara Kruger [Binder 2]"], undated; 207879 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Kruger [1/3], 1982-1985; 207880 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Kruger [2/3], 1985,1986; 207881 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Kruger [3/3], 1986, 1987; 207882 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Guillermo Kuitca Catalogue, 1992, 1993; 207883 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Guillermo Kuitca Financial Correspondence, 1989-1992; 207884 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Guillermo Kuitca: Press, 1991-1992; 207885 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Kuitca Press, 1990, 1991; 207886 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Guillermo Kuitca: Correspondence, 1989-1994; 207887 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Guillermo Kuitca, 1990-1994; 207888 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Gary Lang [1] [1/2], 1984-1993; 207889 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Gary Lang [1] [2/2], 1988-1991; 207891 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - [L], 1980-2005; 207892 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Gary Lang [2], 1988-1992; 207893 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Martin Larralde, 1994-2000; 207894 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Sol Lewitt, 1979-1983, 1995, 2000; 207895 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - [Gernot Linder Correspondence], 2000-2001; 207896 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - [Gernot] Linder, 2001; 207897 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Alfredo Londaibere, 1995; 207898 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Robert Longo, 1980; 207899 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Mark Luyten, 1992-1994; 207900 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - M, 1978-1993; 207901 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Alan McCollum [1], 1987-1993; 207902 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Alan McCollum [2], 1985-1989; 207903 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Hanging Instructions for Allan McCollum "200 Plastic Surrogates", 1993; 207904 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Kim McConnel, 1992-2001; 207905 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Robert Mangold, undated; 207906 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - E. Mattacci - Press Catalogues, 1988-1993; 207907 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Brenda Miller, 1973, 1974; 207908 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Paul Miller, 1995-1996; 207909 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Keith Miller, 1980-1991; 207910 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Helmut Middendorf - Corresp., 1984-1998; 207911 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Helmut Middendorf [1], 1986-2002; 207912 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Helmut Middendorf [2] [1/2], 1984-1999; 207913 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Helmut Middendorf [2] [2/2], 1984-1999; 208410 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Sabina Mirri [1], 1982-1985; 207914 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Sabina Mirri [2], 1985; 207915 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Andy Moses, 1986, 1987; 207916 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Olivier Mosset, 1981-1986; 207917 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Stephen Mueller [1] [1/2], 1984-1998; 207918 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Stephen Mueller [1] [2/2], 1994-1998; 207919 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Stephen Mueller Corresp. [1/2], 1984-1998; 207920 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Stephen Mueller Corresp. [2/2], 1982-1992; 207921 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Stephen Mueller [2] [1/2], 1984-1994; 207926 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Stephen Mueller [2] [2/2], 1986-1994; 207927 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - [Shirin Neshat - Announcements], 1996-2000; 207928 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Shirin Neshat Reviews [1/2], 1993-1997; 207929 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Shirin Neshat Reviews [2/2], undated; 207930 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Neshat: Correspondence with Collectors; Loan agreements for 10th Sydney [1/2], 1996; 207931 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Neshat: Correspondence with Collectors; Loan agreements for 10th Sydney [2/2], 1996; 207932 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Shirin Neshat; Show Cards, Bio, Correspondence, 1995-2000; 207933 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Shirin Neshat; Show Cards, Bio, Correspondence [2/2], 1995-1997; 207934 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Guillermo Kuitca at Sperone; Rome, 1990-1991; 207935 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Peter Nagy, 1987-1988; 207936 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Donald Newman [1], 1979-1991; 207937 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Donald Newman [2], 2002, 2003; 207938 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Nunzio [1], 1985-1991; 207939 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Nunzio [2], 1989; 207940 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - O, 1982-1988; 207941 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Mary Obering [1], 1988; 207942 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Mary Obering [2], 1987-1992; 207943 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Ocampo Press, 1995, 1996; 207945 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Manuel Ocampo [1/2], 1993-1997; 207946 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Manuel Ocampo [2/2], 1987-1996; 207947 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Ocampo, 1993-1998; 207948 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Athos Ongaro, 1983-1986; 207949 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Ongaro, 1988-1996; 207950 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Luigi Ontani, 1982-1992; 207951 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - P/Q, 1976-1992; 207952 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - San Lorenzo Artists, 1984; 207953 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Anna Paparatti, 1994; 207954 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Mimmo Paladino, 1979-1998; 207955 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Mimmo Paladino - Press, 1980-1983; 208107 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Perry, undated; 208108 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Claudio Palmieri [1], 1986-1989; 208109 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Claudio Palmieri [2], 1986; 208111 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Maurizio Pellegrin, 1991-1992; 208112 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Cristiano Pintaldi, 1998-1999; 208113 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Lucio Pozzi, 1979,1982; 208114 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Ramsden, 2003-2004; 208115 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Robert Rauschenberg, undated; 208116 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Robilant, 1998-2001; 208117 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - R, 1976-1994; 208118 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Gert Rappenecker, 1992-1996; 208119 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Rammellzee, 1982-1983; 208120 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Judy Rifka, 1977, 1988; 208121 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Christiane Richter, 1991, 1998; 208122 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Ira Richer - Correspond., 1983-1987; 208123 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Niguel Angel Rios - Press, 1995; 208124 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Daniele Robbiani, undated; 208125 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - [Loose Photographs], undated; 208126 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Robert Ryman, 1981; 208127 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - S [1/2], 1978-1994; 208128 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - S [2/2], 1976-1993; 208129 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - David Salle - Photos, undated; 208130 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - David Salle, 1979-1983; 208131 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Andrea Salvino, 1998, 1999; 208132 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Suzanne Santoro [1/2], 1973-1981; 208133 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Suzanne Santoro [2/2], undated; 210221 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Salomé [Folder from "Salomé + Castelli" Letter Box] [1], 1981-1983; 208134 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Salomé [Folder from "Salomé + Castelli" Letter Box] [2], 1981-1983; 208135 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - [Loose Material from "Salomé + Castelli" Letter Box], 1982, 1983; 208136 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - [Geile Tiere Berlin], 1980; 210119 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      Format: Phonograph records. [10-inch]
      Taken from folder labeled "[Loose Material from "Salomé + Castelli Letter Box]" (Box 31, Folder 29) in series III, subseries A. Moved to separate box for preservation.
    - A [From "Salomé+ Castelli" Letter Box] [1/3], 1981, 1982; 208137 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - A [From "Salomé + Castelli" Letter Box] [2/3], 1981-1983; 208139 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - A [From "Salomé + Castelli" Letter Box] [3/3], 1981; 208140 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Cheri Samba [1], 1990-1997; 208141 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Cheri Samba [2], 1990-2002; 208142 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Salvatore Scarpitta, 1990-1992; 208143 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Mario Schifano, 1982, 1983; 208144 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Julian Schnabel, undated; 208145 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Robert Smithson, 1976; 208146 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - [Teresa Serrano], 1994; 208147 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Teresa Serrano [1], 1994-1996; 208148 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Teresa Serrano [2], 1994-1998; 208149 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - [Amy Sillman], 1994; 208150 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Pablo Siquier, 1996-1998; 208151 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Frank Stella, 1980; 208153 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Randy Stevens, 1980-1992; 208154 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - T, 1981-1993; 208155 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box] [1/5] [Material from Folder "Ernesto Tatafiore], 1980-1983; 208156 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box] [2/5], 1982, 1983; 208157 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box] [3/5], 1981, 1982; 208158 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box] [4/5], 1980-1982; 208159 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box] [5/5], undated; 208160 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Deborah Turbeville, 1997, 1998; 208161 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Marco Tirelli [1], 1984-1992; 208162 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Marco Tirelli [2], undated; 208163 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Cy Twombly, 1977-1986; 208164 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - V/W, 1973-1994; 208165 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Adriana Varejao [1], 1995; 208166 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Adriana Varejao [2], 1994, 1995; 208179 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Jeff Wall, 1983-1987; 208180 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Sokhi Wagner, 1987; 208181 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Jenny Watson [1], 1990-1999; 208182 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Jenny Watson [2] [1/2], 1977-1999; 208183 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Jenny Watson [2] [2/2], 1991-1999; 208481 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - James Welling, 1987; 208184 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Tod Wizon - Press + Corresp., 1977-1987; 208185 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Tom Wudl, 1980-1987; 208186 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - X/Y/Z, 1977-1992; 208187 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: Master Slides Binders, 204162
    This subseries originally consisted of four large binders labeled "Master Slides A-C," "Master Slides C-G," "Master Slides H-M," "Master Slides M-O," and "Master Slides P-Z." This original arrangement has been preserved while the slides were transferred to new, archivally sound sleeves and rehoused in acid-free binders. The material in the binders is divided by tabbed dividers arranged by artists' names.
    Subseries comprises master slides kept by the Annina Nosei Gallery.
    - Master Slides A-C [1/2], undated; 208940 (Album A)
    - Master Slides A-C [2/2], undated; 208941 (Album B)
    - Master Slides C-G [1/2], undated; 208942 (Album C)
    - Master Slides C-G [2/2], undated; 208943 (Album D)
    - Master Slides H-M [1/2], undated; 208944 (Album E)
    - Master Slides H-M [2/2], undated; 208945 (Album F)
    - Master Slides M-O, undated; 208946 (Album G)
    - Master Slides P-Z [1/2], undated; 208947 (Album H)
    - Master Slides P-Z [2/2], undated; 208948 (Album I)
  - Subseries C: Visuals Binders, 205262
    This subseries originally comprised one binder per artist. This original arrangement has been preserved while the visual materials were transferred to new, archivally sound sleeves and rehoused in acid-free binders.
    The original binder labels have been reproduced here, except for what appears between brackets ("[ ]"), such information was provided by the archivist for ease of use.
    Some transparencies were originally sleeved in mylar, labeled, and placed in one of eight numbered pockets in a single mylar sleeve. For preservation reasons, the original sleeve was discarded. The transparencies are placed in archivally sound plastic sleeves, and a note is included that reproduces the original numbering, usually in the form, "From Binder Sleeve Pocket Numbered 'x.'"
    Many of the original sleeves in the binders contained several [elements]. Each [element] has been separated out, placed in its own sleeve, and placed in a new binder following a cover sheet giving the original binder sleeve's order (e.g., Binder Sleeve 2/7), the series and subseries, and the name of the artist as it appeared on the original binder.
    When an original sleeve or binder pocket contained a large majority of paper-based [elements], everything in that sleeve or pocket was removed and placed in a folder that can be found in ["Subseries D: Material Separated"].
    If the original sleeve or pocket contained a large amount of photographic material as well as paper-based material, then the paper material is removed to a folder labelled with the binder's name followed by the phrase "From Binder Sleeve x/y," and the photographic material is resleeved and arranged as described above.
    In some cases, a binder sleeve with four pockets will contain four or more 3"x5" transparencies in plastic sleeves with a card or sticker taped to the sleeve giving the piece's name and dimensions. Each individually sleeved transparency is taken out of its sleeve and placed in an archival three-pocket mylar sleeve. The original plastic sleeve, if it has bears notations, is placed in the same sleeve as the transparency, along with the card or sticker that bears infomation on the artwork pictured.
    The entire contents of [Izumi Chiaraluce Binder] have been moved to Series III, Subseries E, and will not appear in Series III, Subseries C.
    Series comprises visual materials (photographic prints, transparencies, slides, negatives, etc.) and other promotional material (including artists' bios and price lists) accumulated by the Annina Nosei Gallery.
    - Ghada Amer, undated; 208949 (Album J)
    - Karel Appel; Francois Boisrond; Georges Rousse, undated; 208950 (Album K)
    - Argentina; Fabian Burgos; Pablo Siquier; Martin Larralde, undated; 208951 (Album L)
    - David Bowes; David Deutsch; Keith Milow, undated; 208952 (Album M)
    - Nancy Bowen; Ellen Brooks [1/2], undated; 208953 (Album N)
    - Nancy Bowen; Ellen Brooks [2/2], undated; 208954 (Album O)
    - Fabian Burgos, undated; 208955 (Album P)
    - Pizzi Cannella, undated; 208956 (Album Q)
    - Chuck Connelly, undated; 208957 (Album R)
    - Fernando Canovas, undated; 208958 (Album S)
    - Ceccobelli; Chia; Commandeur; Colombo, undated; 208960 (Album T)
    - [Arturo Duclos], undated; 208961 (Album U)
    - Arturo Elizondo, undated; 208962 (Album V)
    - Pietro Fortuna, Tomarchio Levi, Ronald Gault Jirado, undated; 208963 (Album W)
    - [Julio] Galan [1/2], undated; 208964 (Album X)
    - [Julio] Galan [2/2], undated; 208965 (Album Y)
    - [Julio] Galan New [1/2], undated; 208966 (Album Z)
    - [Julio] Galan New [2/2], undated; 208967 (Album AA)
    - Daniele Galliano, undated; 208968 (Album AB)
    - Vincent Gallo, undated; 208971 (Album AC)
    - Tsibi Geva [1/2], undated; 208969 (Album AD)
    - Tsibi Geva [2/2], undated; 208970 (Album AE)
    - Graciela Hasper, undated; 208972 (Album AF)
    - K.H. Hodicke, Koberling, undated; 208973 (Album AG)
    - [Guillermo] Kuitca [1], undated; 208974 (Album AH)
    - [Guillermo] Kuitca [2], undated; 208975 (Album AI)
    - Helmut Middendorf, undated; 208976 (Album AJ)
    - Paul D. Miller, Gian Marco Montesano, undated; 208977 (Album AK)
    - Sabina Mirri, Schifano, undated; 208978 (Album AL)
    - Stephen Mueller, undated; 208979 (Album AM)
    - Shirin Neshat Slides; Shirin Neshat Inventory, undated; 208985 (Album AN)
    - Donald Newman [1/2], undated; 208982 (Album AO)
    - Donald Newman [2/2], undated; 208983 (Album AP)
    - Nunzio, undated; 208984 (Album AQ)
    - Mary Oberling, Beth Brenner, undated; 208980 (Album AR)
    - Manuel Ocampo, undated; 208981 (Album AS)
    - Palmieri Paladino [1/2], undated; 208986 (Album AT)
    - Palmieri Paladino [2/2], undated; 208987 (Album AU)
    - Liliana Porter, undated; 208988 (Album AV)